Be careful what you pray for
The Crucifixion is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Xavier Gens.
When a priest is jailed for the murder of a nun on whom he was performing an exorcism, an investigative journalist strives to
determine whether he in fact murdered a mentally ill person, or if he lost the battle with a demonic presence.
Nicole Rawlins, played by Sophie Cookson.
Father Anton, played by Corneliu Ulici.
Sister Adelina Marinescu, played by Ada Lupu.
Vaduva, played by Brittany Ashworth.
Bishop Gornik, played by Mathew Zajac.
Exorcism nun, played by Diana Vladu.
The Crucifixion is a 2017 horror film directed by Xavier
Gens, written by Chad Hayes and Carey W.
Hayes and starring Sophie Cookson, Brittany Ashworth and Corneliu Ulici.
It is based on the Tanacu exorcism that took place
in Vaslui County, Romania, in 2005.
The film explores themes of prison, newspaper, journalist, nun, investigation.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.